hey what's up in this video I want to
talk about how to build your business if
you lack the time or financial resources
to do so you know I made a lot of people
where this is their situation that
they're in and I get it you know I have
two kids under two years old I lack the
time resources that most people do to
build a business even record videos like
this but what I've done is I've
developed strategies to be able to do
this over the last couple of years and
part of what we Mentor people on is how
to automate your business as well as
create Evergreen marketing that that way
you don't have to be working tons of
hours to be able to do the stuff in your
business to get them done and what I've
noticed is actually one of the biggest
things that stops people is not that
they lack time or finances but it's
rather they just don't know what to do
and they don't they've never thought
about it creatively and then they're
being harsh and critical of themselves
that they don't know these things like
as if they were supposed to know them
already can I tell you this like it's
not anybody's fault at all that you
don't know this stuff and so that's why
I'm making this video right here because
I actually want to give you some of
those ideas and resources what I do
every single day for those of you that I
haven't met is I help coaches mentors
trainers course creators scale their
businesses to multiple six and seven
figures I personally built multiple
businesses in this space over eight
Figures it's over $10 million a year in
profit and I Mentor people every single
day on doing this their business and and
this constantly comes up because I can
teach you all the strategies for your
marketing for promotion social media
content
creation uh sales lead generation
funnels all of
that but at the end of the day um if
you're not executing getting stuff out
there cons consistantly promoting your
business and and you're and you find
that you don't have the time to do so or
maybe of the time that you do you don't
want to do it you feel demotivated you
it's not fun for you maybe you're
dreading it um or you just simply just
don't have the time period and and
because you don't have the time um you
also don't have the finances to hire
other people to do it for you and so
that's
generally the people that I work with
the most is fall into that category
because again that's
that's what I believe is if you're able
to know how to overcome that limitation
nothing is impossible for you and so
without having the financial resources
to hire other people and Outsource I
would recommend Outsourcing as quickly
as possible and and I'm going to talk
about a little bit about Outsourcing in
this video but um for most people that's
not an option for them because they
don't have the finances to be able to
Outsource Outsourcing means hiring
people to be able to do the stuff for
them to build their landing pages to
build their funnels to to create all
this stuff and depending on if you're
hiring people
overseas um you know that might run you
a couple thousand dollars a month to do
that and if you're hiring people locally
in European or Western American
economies you're going to be in the
range of tens of thousands of dollars a
month in salaries just to have other
people doing the work for you and that's
actually a normal going low end of the
spectrum rate right there okay in my own
business I have a team that's a hybrid I
got a couple of people here in the
United States I got some people that
work for me in the in the Philippines
and combined uh salaries just to grow my
business it's about it's about two grand
a month and so I'm spending this about
two grand a month about $25,000 a year
uh to scale my business and now what's
awesome is I only work 10 hours a week
in my business so what I've done is I've
figured out okay I got maybe two hours a
day to build my business that I want to
like really focus building my business
work and then I Outsource the rest of
the activities um but what would you do
if you don't have the ability to
Outsource that's what I want to talk
about today is I want to talk about what
do you do if you lack the time and
financial resources number one you have
to make the time for what you have to
get done done you're going to have to
carve out like at least an hour or two a
day to build a business of some kind if
you have a business if you want to build
a business and this is one of the
biggest uh
areas that listen if you're unwilling to
do this you're going to
struggle you know give up Netflix time
give up video gaming time give up and by
the way I I love Netflix and video games
myself I love reading novels I love this
type of stuff but like sometimes certain
priorities are more important certain
things are more important and so you
know maybe like for me sometimes the
baby's taking a nap football might be on
I love football uh but I got to go
record a piece of content here real
quick and I'm going to take that time
because I'm prioritizing what's
important in those time slots and so
it's important to actually make the time
for what we can do and that's where what
what we end up really realizing and and
it all boils down to is a couple of
things we're we're
overthinking everything we're allowing
perfectionism to get in there we're
allowing the fear of is it going to be
uh accepted by other people what are
other people going to think about the
things that we do and then this ends up
bubbling up inside of us and then that's
where a lot of times that I find is
people's time management the reason why
they're procrastinating the reason why
they're not doing the work is actually
stuff that's beneath the surface that
they're trying to avoid stuff that's
uncomfortable that they don't want to
talk about that they don't that they
don't want to look at okay and so for
you to actually go ahead and
successfully build your business we
cannot allow perfectionism to control us
we cannot allow that need for it to all
be
perfect doing everything perfect is not
a spirit of Excellence it's not it's
actually the very opposite of it because
there's no such thing as perfect and
things can always be improved upon and
so done is better than perfect and what
I find is this is that actually having
time constraints having artificial
deadlines having a limited amount of
time to get stuff done you know today I
I gave myself 30 minutes to write a
sales letter for a client that was
paying me tens of thousands of dollars
to to do this in their business but I
really only had like 30 minutes to do
this so what I did was I was able to in
that constraint I wrote the I wrote an
incredible sales letter in 30 minutes
I'm going to review it
tomorrow and and it's going to close
millions of dollars in sales for the
client I know it is because the last
sales letter we created them did that
and the one before that did that as well
okay and so in this the time constraint
allowed me to get really focused with my
time and then moving past the
perfectionism moving past the
overthinking and often times again we
got to look at what is beneath the
surface one of the things that we might
need to do is find enjoyment in doing
things that we maybe dislike
doing find enjoyment in doing things
that we dread that we're fearful about
that we're not sure is this going to be
comfortable and I find that human beings
we have an incredible ability to do this
to endure hardship this is unfortunately
why people find themselves in abusive
relationships is one of the pieces why
is because they can they can endure
abuse for a long period of time now
we're not talking about abuse here we're
not talking about self abuse here but
we're talking about the fact that
sometimes in your business there are
activities there are things you don't
know how to do there are things that
maybe you dread doing there are things
that you just feel
like you're going to cry when you do
it if you can train your brain to find
enjoyment in doing those things you
shift your
perspective to where you're enjoying
doing the hard things to where you're
finding it fun to do those
things you will be able to do far more
than you ever imagined and then it's all
about being consistent it's all about
consistently showing up it's about
putting yourself out there to people
marketing your business promoting it and
every single week being a reliable
resource and Authority in your field
somebody that people can look up to a
resource that solves a problem for
people that are out there when you can
do this you know my YouTube channel is
that for people it's a resource people
can come to to learn and to grow in
their business my coaching program is a
resource for this I've developed the
structure and the systems in my life and
in my business to be able to do
this but it's about showing up and it's
about doing the work okay and so if you
lack the time we got to make the time
and if we lack the finances we got to do
the things that we don't want to do
those are really the only options that
we have and so how can we make the best
of that and Rise Above
This and often times what ends up
happening is we end up overthinking the
process we're we're stuck in analysis
paralysis we're stuck in uh trying to
make
everything perfect we're struggling to
make the decisions of what we should do
we're unsure of what decisions to make
that's where having the power of being
in a community in a coaching group is
really amazing having the accountability
of being in a group like that like what
we have in my client growth accelerator
program where you can bounce ideas off
of other people where you can ask for
help on things that you're unsure about
and you can get clarity and focus on
what are the activities that are really
really going to move the needle forward
for you and so if you find yourself
struggling in these ways one of the best
things that you can do is get around a
community of people that are actually
doing the work that are actually doing
the hard things okay and then from there
you start to do the individual stuff
building out your landing page growing
your email
list building out a lead
magnet starting to do webinars
presentations maybe launch an ebook
launch uh a video course that then you
can use or a mini class that then sells
people on your coaching or your or your
programs and that might sound daunting
to you today that might sound like oh my
gosh it's just so much work then I got
to make social media content then I got
to promote it then I got to do all that
just take it one step at a time just
take it one piece at a time what's going
to end up happening is that all the
stuff you have to do in your business
it's going to become like autopilot it's
going to become like something that's as
easy as breathing for you and it's the
same as when you wake up in the morning
and you brush your teeth it's just part
of what you do every day that's what it
is for me in my business is I've
literally created a habit structure in
my life in my business of doing the
stuff that moves the needle forward I
have a habit and a routine structure
that allows me to not let my excuses
take over okay lack time today I have a
structure that I'm going to shift things
to tomorrow and if I shift it more than
two days how do I adjust for that and
those are systems that we can start to
develop inside of our life to be able to
accomplish far
greater than we ever
imagined just by simply uh White
knuckling it or just trying to push
forward what you want to do is you want
to get into a flow state where you're
not white knuckling where you're not
striving I don't strive in my business I
don't strive in my personal life I don't
strive in my
finances I go with the flow and I've
created a flow where every day is fun
exciting and I show up and everything
just works it's a system that works and
it comes
together and I get to work from home and
I get to spend time with my family and I
get to have a life that I only ever
dreamed of years
ago and that's exactly what you can have
as well and so again if if that's
something that you want I'd love to work
with you in my client growth accelerator
program I'd love to walk with you
through how do you set up all these
different things in your business how do
you actually create the resources that
you need how do you start promoting your
business how do you grow your email list
and generate leads how do you Market to
people the right way and then how do you
sell to them so you can have consistent
income so that you can have massive
impact and so that things are dialed in
to where you have the financial and time
Freedom that you want that's exactly
what we do inside of my client growth
accelerator program every single week
I'd love to work with you in that make
sure to check out some of the free
classes that we have below this video
and stay plugged in to our
content if you got any questions reach
out to me on Instagram or X or Facebook
or even in the comments below this video
and listen I know no matter what
situation you're in you can accomplish
great things you're not stuck you're not
limited by just your
situation you can do far greater than
you ever
imagined when you just decide to stay
focused to stay consistent to not let
your excuses take
over you know it might it might sound
harsh to say
that but just take it one step at a time
one hard thing that you've been putting
off that you can say I dread doing this
but let me see if I can find some fun
and enjoyment in it maybe it's learning
a new class maybe it's watching another
YouTube video or a couple of the
different YouTube videos that are on
this channel right here that might be a
great thing for you to do a great
practice for you if you're watching this
right now watch some of the other
YouTube videos that we have on here and
then start to implement start to do the
individual
steps start to develop out your sales
copy create your landing pages start
promoting offers growing your email list
and selling to create the kind of
business that you want okay so this has
been great I've had a great time talking
here today with you would love to see
you in my accelerator program we'll talk
soon how going